A Guide to the Russell Sage Foundation records FA015
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Russell Sage Foundation records, 1974-2002; 2; 120 Cubic Feet 252 document boxes.
  - Administrative, 1907-2001; 1; 23.3 Cubic Feet
    - Finance Committee, 1944-1996; 1970-1996; 4
      - Meeting, 1976 February 9 (Box 31, Folder 327)
      - Meeting, 1976 May 14 (Box 31, Folder 328)
      - Meeting, 1976 August 19 (Box 31, Folder 329)
      - Meeting, 1976 December 1 (Box 31, Folder 330)
      - Meeting, 1977 January 7 (Box 31, Folder 331)
      - Meeting, 1977 March 10 (Box 31, Folder 332)
      - Meeting, 1977 June 3 (Box 31, Folder 333)
      - Meeting, 1977 August 19 (Box 31, Folder 334)
      - Meeting, 1977 September 13 (Box 32, Folder 335)
      - Meeting, 1977 November 21 (Box 32, Folder 336)
      - Meeting, Cancelled, 1978 February 3 (Box 32, Folder 337)
      - Meeting, 1978 April 18 (Box 32, Folder 338)
      - Meeting, 1978 August 16 (Box 32, Folder 339)
      - Meeting, 1978 November 8 (Box 32, Folder 340)
      - Meeting, 1979 February 8 (Box 32, Folder 341)
      - Meeting, 1979 May 22 (Box 32, Folder 342)
      - Meeting, 1979 August 21 (Box 32, Folder 343)
      - Meeting, 1979 December 6 (Box 33, Folder 344)
      - Meeting, 1980 February 11 (Box 33, Folder 345)
      - Meeting, 1980 June 12 (Box 33, Folder 346)
      - Meeting, 1980 October 24 (Box 33, Folder 347)
      - Meeting, 1981 March 2 (Box 33, Folder 348)
      - Meeting, 1981 May 21 (Box 33, Folder 349)
      - Meeting, 1981 October 26 (Box 34, Folder 350)
      - Meeting, 1982 March 1-2 (Box 34, Folder 351)
      - Meeting, 1982 June 7 (Box 34, Folder 352)
      - Meeting, 1982 November 1 (Box 34, Folder 353)
      - Meeting, 1983 February 28 (Box 34, Folder 354)
      - Meeting, 1983 June 6 (Box 35, Folder 355)
      - Meeting, 1983 October 17 (Box 35, Folder 356)
      - Meeting, 1984 February 8 (Box 35, Folder 357)
      - Meeting, 1984 May 25 (Box 35, Folder 358)
      - Meeting, 1984 October 23 (Box 35, Folder 359)
      - Meeting, 1985 March 11 (Box 35, Folder 360)
      - Meeting, 1985 June 5 (Box 35, Folder 361)
      - Meeting, 1985 November 1 (Box 35, Folder 362)
      - Meeting, 1986 March 10 (Box 35, Folder 363)
      - Meeting, 1986 June 25 (Box 35, Folder 364)
      - Meeting, 1986 December 1 (Box 35, Folder 365)
      - Meeting, 1987 March 23 (Box 35, Folder 366)
      - Meeting, 1987 June 18 (Box 35, Folder 367)
      - Meeting, 1987 Novmeber 20 (Box 36, Folder 368)
      - Meeting, 1988 March 21 (Box 36, Folder 369)
      - Meeting, 1988 June 10 (Box 36, Folder 370)
      - Meeting, 1988 October 14 (Box 36, Folder 371)
      - Meeting, 1989 February 28 (Box 36, Folder 372)
      - Meeting, 1989 June14 (Box 36, Folder 373)
      - Meeting, 1989 October 19 (Box 36, Folder 374)
      - Meeting, 1990 February 27 (Box 36, Folder 375)
      - Meeting, 1990 June 21 (Box 36, Folder 376)
      - Meeting, 1990 November 2 (Box 37, Folder 377)
      - Meeting, 1991 February 21 (Box 37, Folder 378)
      - Meeting, 1991 June 20 (Box 37, Folder 379)
      - Meeting, 1991 November 1 (Box 37, Folder 380)
      - Meeting, 1992 February 26 (Box 37, Folder 381)
      - Meeting, 1992 June 19 (Box 37, Folder 382)
      - Meeting, Asset Allocation-Working File, 1992 June 19 (Box 37, Folder 383)
      - Meeting, Asset Allocation-Originals, 1992 June 19 (Box 37, Folder 384)
      - Meeting, 1992 November 6 (Box 38, Folder 385)
      - Meeting, 1993 February 2 (Box 38, Folder 386)
      - Meeting, 1993 May 4 (Box 38, Folder 387)
      - Meeting, 1993 November 5 (Box 38, Folder 388)
      - Meeting, 1994 February 23 (Box 38, Folder 389)
      - Meeting, 1994 June 16 (Box 39, Folder 390)
      - Meeting, 1994 November 11 (Box 39, Folder 391)
      - Meeting, 1995 February 22 (Box 39, Folder 392)
      - Meeting, 1995 June 20 (Box 39, Folder 393)
      - Meeting, 1995 November 3 (Box 39, Folder 394)
      - Meeting, 1996 February 26 (Box 40, Folder 395)
      - Meeting, 1996 June 21 (Box 40, Folder 396)
      - Orders, 1944-1966 (Box 40, Folder 397)
    - Presidential Papers, 1964-1986; 5
      - Brim, Orville G., Jr., News from Resignation, 1971 June 11 (Box 40, Folder 398)
      - News Releases, 1964-1967 (Box 40, Folder 399)
      - Cline, Hugh F., 1976 (Box 40, Folder 400)
      - Wildavsky, Aaron, Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 401)
      - Wildavsky, Aaron, Correspondence and Publications, 1974 & 1976; 1976 (Box 41, Folder 402)
      - Wildavsky, Aaron, Correspondence and Publications, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 403)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 404)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1983 January-June (Box 41, Folder 405)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1983 July-December (Box 41, Folder 406)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1984 January-March (Box 41, Folder 407)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1984 April-May (Box 42, Folder 408)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1984 June-August (Box 42, Folder 409)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1984 September-December (Box 42, Folder 410)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1985 January-February (Box 42, Folder 411)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1985 March-June (Box 42, Folder 412)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1985 July (Box 43, Folder 413)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1985 August-September (Box 43, Folder 414)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1985 October-December (Box 43, Folder 415)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1986 January-April (Box 43, Folder 416)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1986 May-September (Box 43, Folder 417)
      - Robinson, Marshall, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 418)
      - Robinson, Marshall, Basic Books, 1980-1983 (Box 44, Folder 419)
      - Robinson, Marshall, Conferences, Meetings, etc., 1986 (Box 44, Folder 420)
      - Robinson, Marshall, Council on Foundations, 1977-1981 (Box 44, Folder 421)
      - Robinson, Marshall, Dissemination of Research at Russell Sage Foundation, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 422)
      - Robinson, Marshall, Expenditures, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 423)
      - Robinson, Marshall, Independent Sector, 1981-1986 (Box 44, Folder 424)
      - Robinson, Marshall, Memoranda to Russell Sage Foundation Staff, 1979-1986 (Box 44, Folder 425)
      - Robinson, Marshall, National Planning Association, Committee on New American Realities, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 426)
      - Robinson, Marshall, The New York Academy of Sciences, Science Policy Association, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 427)
      - Robinson, Marshall, New York Community Trust, Luncheon Group: New York City Grant-Making Executives, 1980-1986 (Box 44, Folder 428)
      - Robinson, Marshall, New York Times, 1982 March 7 (Box 44, Folder 429)
      - Robinson, Marshall, Russell Sage Foundation Office Publications, 1980-1983 (Box 44, Folder 430)
      - Robinson, Marshall, Russell Sage Foundation List of Publications, 1964-1978 (Box 44, Folder 431)
      - Robinson, Marshall, Russell Sage Foundation Program Committee, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 432)
      - Robinson, Marshall, Seminars, 1979-1985 (Box 44, Folder 433)
      - Marshall Robinson Files (Box 44A)
        Restricted - pending further processing.
    - Presidential Search, 1975-1986; 6
      - Candidates, 1975-1978 (Box 45, Folder 434)
      - Candidates, 1975-1978 (Box 45, Folder 434A)
      - Correspondence, Kay, Herma Hill, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 435)
      - Trustees, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 436)
      - Candidates, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 437)
      - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 438)
      - Notes, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 439)
      - Presidential Search Committee, Interviews, 1985 January 13-14 (Box 46, Folder 440)
      - Presidential Search Committee, Interviews, 1985 January 13-14 (Box 46, Folder 441)
      - Presidential Search Committee, 1985 August 27 (Box 46, Folder 442)
      - Presidential Search Committee, 1985 August 27 (Box 46, Folder 442A)
      - Presidnetial Search Committee, 1985 November 26 (Box 45, Folder 443)
      - Candidates, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 444)
      - Candidates, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 445)
      - Candidates, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 446)
      - Candidates, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 446A)
      - Candidates, 1985-1986 (Box 46, Folder 447)
      - Candidates, 1985-1986 (Box 46, Folder 447A)
      - Notes, 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 448)
      - Resignation of Marshall Robinson, 1985 July 10 (Box 47, Folder 449)
      - Telegrams, Eric Wanner, 1986 June (Box 47, Folder 450)
    - Financial, 1907-1976; 7
      - Income Accounts, 1911-1923 (Box 48, Folder 451)
      - Income Accounts, 1924-1939 (Box 48, Folder 452)
      - Income Cash, 1907-1915 (Box 48, Folder 453)
      - Income, Principal, 1913-1927 (Box 48, Folder 454)
      - Income, Principal, 1928-1939 (Box 49, Folder 455)
      - Income, Principal, 1943-1947 (Box 49, Folder 456)
      - Income, Principal, 1941-1947 (Box 49, Folder 457)
      - Income and Principal, Receipts and Disbursements, 1907-1911 (Box 49, Folder 458)
      - Principal Account, 1940-1942, 1947; 1940-1942 (Box 50, Folder 459)
      - Principal Account, 1940-1942 (Box 50, Folder 460)
      - Principal Account, 1943-1944 (Box 50, Folder 461)
      - Principal Account, 1945-1947 (Box 50, Folder 462)
      - Principal Account Statements, 1913-1922 (Box 50, Folder 463)
      - Principal Account Statements, 1923-1930 (Box 51, Folder 464)
      - Principal Account Statements, 1931-1940 (Box 51, Folder 465)
      - Accountants' Reports, 1945-1948 (Box 51, Folder 466)
      - Amortization of Bond Premiums, 1907, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 467)
      - Bowery Savings Bank-CD's, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 468)
      - Half Year Reports, 1951, 1954-1958 (Box 52, Folder 469)
      - Report of Examination, 1950-1953 (Box 52, Folder 470)
      - Review of Investments, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 471)
      - Review of Investments, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 472)
      - Review of Investments, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 473)
      - Review of Investments, 1957 (Box 52, Folder 474)
      - Review of Investments, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 475)
      - Review of Investments, 1959-1961 (Box 53, Folder 476)
      - Review of Investments, 1965-1969 (Box 53, Folder 477)
      - Review of Investments, 1970-1971 (Box 53, Folder 478)
      - Russell Sage Foundation Institute of Pathology, Income, 1941-1947, 1950, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 479)
      - Publications, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 480)
  - Marsh Island, 1916-1986; 2; 2.4 Cubic Feet
    - Deeds, 1916-1920 (Box 54, Folder 481)
    - Certificates of Sale and Copies of Acts, 1920 & 1944 (Box 54, Folder 482)
    - Lease and Agreements, 1950-1954 (Box 54, Folder 483)
    - History of Leases and Act No. 157 of Louisiana Legislature, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 484)
    - Geophysical Permits Nos. 4233 & 4234, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 485)
    - Letter of Modification and Lease Nos. 3026, 3027 & 3028, 1955-1956 (Box 54, Folder 486)
    - Geophysical Permit No. 6175, Act No. 136 and Lease Nos. 3498 & 3499, 1958-1959 (Box 54, Folder 487)
    - Admendment to State Lease 1814, Lease Nos. 4090, 4091, 4092 & 4093, 1961-1963 (Box 54, Folder 488)
    - Lease Nos. 4094, 4095, 4096, 4097 & 4206 and Permits 9922 & 9923, 1963-1964 (Box 54, Folder 489)
    - Lease Nos. 4647 & 4648, Permit 1448-P, Unitization Agreement and Counterpart Copy of Unitization Agreement, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 490)
    - Unitizations Agreements, Wildlife Fisheries Commission Agreement, Royalities, Division Orders Nos. 33391 & 33390 and Receipts, 1944-1970 (Box 55, Folder 491)
    - Abstract Title No. 4464A, 1926 (Box 55, Folder 492)
    - Alligator and Wildlife Information, 1971-1976 (Box 55, Folder 493)
    - Amoco, 1979, 1984-1985 (Box 55, Folder 494)
    - Appraisal of Royalty Interest, Atwater, Cowan, Carter, Miller & Heffner, 1971-1982 (Box 55, Folder 495)
    - Chronology of Documents, 1920-1980 (Box 56, Folder 496)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973 & 1982 (Box 56, Folder 497)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1976 (Box 56, Folder 498)
    - Correspondence, 1980 & 1983 (Box 56, Folder 499)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 500)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 501)
    - Correspondence and Statements, 1976 & 1986 (Box 57, Folder 502)
    - State of Louisiana State Mineral Board, 1949-1957 (Box 57, Folder 503)
    - Cashco Oil Company, 1982-1984 (Box 57, Folder 504)
    - Crude Oil Windfall, Profit Tax of 1980, 1980-1985 (Box 57, Folder 505)
    - Deed of Donation, Memorandum of Understanding, 1963-1979 (Box 57, Folder 506)
    - General I, 1983-1985 (Box 57, Folder 507)
    - General II, 1984-1985 & 1988 (Box 57, Folder 508)
    - General, Bill Collins Memorandum-Analysis of Marsh Island Production, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 509)
    - General, Louisiana Articles, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 510)
    - Environment, 1978-1983 (Box 58, Folder 511)
    - Environmental Issues, 1982 & 1986 (Box 58, Folder 512)
    - Establishment of Trust Fund, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 513)
    - Exxon, 1980 & 1983 (Box 58, Folder 514)
    - Exxon, 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 515)
    - Exxon & Amoco, 1972-1975 (Box 58, Folder 516)
    - Exxon & Amoco, 1976-1980 (Box 59, Folder 517)
    - Financial Statements, 1974-1984 (Box 59, Folder 518)
    - Finanical Statements, 1973, 1984-1986 (Box 59, Folder 519)
    - Financial Statements From Treasurer & Wildlife and Fisheries Commission, Arthur Anderson & Co., 1968-1979 (Box 59, Folder 520)
    - Financial Statements From Treasurer & Wildlife and Fisheries Commission, Marsh Island-State, 1971-1979 (Box 59, Folder 521)
    - Galveston, Texas, undated (Box 59, Folder 521)
    - Gould-Texas Property, 1950-1952 (Box 59, Folder 523)
    - Internal Revenue Service Technical Advice Memorandum, 1980-1982 (Box 59, Folder 524)
    - Internal Revenue Service Advice Request, 1975-1978 (Box 59, Folder 525)
    - Leases, General, 1982-1986 (Box 60, Folder 526)
    - Leases/Permits/Bids, 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 527)
    - Leases 6538, 6587, 6589 & 6590, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 528)
    - Leases 10224, 10225, 10226, 10227 & 10228, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 529)
    - Leases 11056 & 11057, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 530)
    - Lease Sale, No Bids, 1982 December 15, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 531)
    - State Leases 11056 & 11057, 1984-1986 (Box 60, Folder 532)
    - Letters, 1949-1972 (Box 60, Folder 533)
    - Letters, etc., 1958-1969 (Box 60, Folder 534)
    - Memorandum of Fact, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 535)
    - Milling, Benson, Woodward, Hillyer, Pierson, 1957 & 1968-1979 (Box 61, Folder 536)
    - Milling, Benson Bills, 1975-1982 (Box 61, Folder 537)
    - Milling, Benson Geophysical Permits, 1971-1979 (Box 61, Folder 538)
    - Minutes, 1944-1950 (Box 61, Folder 539)
    - Office of Coastal Zone Management, Final Environmental Impact Statement, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 540)
    - Oil Revenue as Capital, 1963-1975 (Box 61, Folder 541)
    - Photoalbum, undated (Box 61, Folder 542)
    - Receipts, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 543)
    - Rockefeller Wildlife Refuge, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 544)
    - Royalty Payments, 1966-1984 (Box 61, Folder 545)
    - "Set-Aside Appilcation", 1972-1976 (Box 61, Folder 546)
    - Set Aside Internal Revenue Service, 1974-1975 (Box 62, Folder 547)
    - Shell Dredging Lease, 1951 & 1970-1976 (Box 62, Folder 548)
    - State Treasurer 's Reports and Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box 62, Folder 549)
    - Sun Oil Company, 1974-1976 (Box 62, Folder 550)
    - Texas General Drilling, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 551)
    - Title Claims, 1970-1976 (Box 62, Folder 552)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 1983-1986 (Box 62, Folder 553)
    - Treasurer's and Wildlife & Fisheries' Reports, $5,000,000.00 Marsh Island Refuge Fund, 1979-1985 (Box 62, Folder 554)
    - Treasurer's and Wildlife & Fisheries' Reports, Trip, 1974 & 1976 (Box 62, Folder 555)
    - Visit by Trustees, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 556)
    - Wildlife & Fisheries Commission, Financial Statements and Correspondence, 1969-1985 (Box 63, Folder 557)
    - Wildlife & Fisheries, Reports and Studies, 1969-1977 (Box 63, Folder 558)
  - Grants, 1974-2002; 3; 52.5 Cubic Feet
    - Aaron, Henry J., Behavioral Approaches to Policy Analysis: Applications to Retirement and Retirement Policy, 98-96-07, 1995-2000 (Box 63, Folder 559)
    - Aaron, Henry J., Behavioral Approaches to Policy Analysis: Applications to Retirement and Retirement Policy, 98-96-07, 1995-2000 (Box 63, Folder 559A)
    - Aaron, Henry J., Behavioral Approaches to Policy Analysis: Applications to Retirement and Retirement Policy, 98-96-07, Monograph, 1995-2000 (Box 63, Folder 560)
    - Abella, Manolo, Achieving Equality in Employment for Migrant Workers, 97-00-04, 2000-2001 (Box 64, Folder 561)
    - Abella, Manolo, Achieving Equality in Employment for Migrant Workers, 97-00-04, 2000-2001 (Box 64, Folder 561A)
    - Abelson, Robert, A Research Seminar and Seed Money for Pilot Research on the Social Psychological Dynamics of Conflict Between Ethnic and Racial Groups, 978.729, 1991-1994 (Box 64, Folder 562)
    - Abelson, Robert, A Research Seminar and Seed Money for Pilot Research on the Social Psychological Dynamics of Conflict Between Ethnic and Racial Groups, 978.729, 1991-1994 (Box 64, Folder 562A)
    - Abelson, Robert and Donald Green, Pilot Project on Interethnic Conflict, 879.302, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 563)
    - Abelson, Robert and Donald Green, Hate Crimes: Policy and Research, 879.502, 1994-1996 (Box 64, Folder 564)
    - Aidala, Angela A., Presidential Grant, Ideological Experiments and Institutional Change, 1984-1987 (Box 64, Folder 565)
    - Alexander, Jeffery C., Presidential Grant, Watergate Crisis and American Political Culture, 1981-1987 (Box 64, Folder 566)
    - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, John Voss & Harvey Brooks, International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis, 1982-1984 (Box 64, Folder 567)
    - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, John Voss & Corinne S. Schelling, Values in Nature and the Environment, 1978-1989 (Box 65, Folder 568)
    - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, John Voss & Corinne S. Schelling, Values in Nature and the Environment, Attachment File, 1976-1978 (Box 65, Folder 569)
    - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, John Voss & Corinne S. Schelling, Values in Nature and the Environment, Attachment File, 1977-1980 (Box 65, Folder 570)
    - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, John Voss & Corinne S. Schelling, Values in Nature and the Environment, Attachment File, 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 571)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 150th National Meeting of the American Assocation for the Advancement of Science, 1984-1985 (Box 65, Folder 572)
    - American Psychological Association, Melvin Robert Novick, Joint Technical Standards for Educational and Psychological Testing, 1978-1986 (Box 65, Folder 573)
    - American Psychological Association, Melvin Robert Novick, Joint Technical Standards for Educational and Psychological Testing, 1978-1986 (Box 65, Folder 573A)
    - American Psychological Association, Melvin Robert Novick, Joint Technical Standards for Educational and Psychological Testing, Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 66, Folder 574)
    - American Statisical Assocation, Fred C. Leone, Committee on Professional Assocations on Federal Statistics (COPAFS), 1978-1984 (Box 66, Folder 575)
    - American Statisical Assocation, Fred C. Leone, Committee on Professional Assocations on Federal Statistics (COPAFS), 1981-1984 (Box 66, Folder 576)
    - Andreassen, Paul B., Presidential Grant, Judgemental Extrapolation and Market Overreaction, 988.926, 1989-1996 (Box 66, Folder 577)
    - Andreassen, Paul B., Presidential Grant, Judgemental Extrapolation and Market Overreaction, 988.926, 1989-1996 (Box 66, Folder 577A)
    - Art Commission of New York, Presidential Grant, To Complete Fund Raising Program Designed to Restore the Governor's Room at City Hall, 1983-1984 (Box 66, Folder 578)
    - Arthur, Brian, A Workshop on Learning Economics, Psychology and Computer Science, 1990-1996 (Box 66, Folder 579)
    - Arthur, Brian, A Workshop on Learning Economics, Psychology and Computer Science, 1990-1996 (Box 66, Folder 579A)
    - Arthur, Brian, A Workshop on Learning Economics, Psychology and Computer Science, Reports and Working Papers, 1991-1993 (Box 66, Folder 580)
    - Badillo, David A., Presidential Grant, Hispanic Urbanization in New York City, San Antonio and Miami, 1940-1965, 1985-1997 (Box 67, Folder 581)
    - Badillo, David A., Presidential Grant, Hispanic Urbanization in New York City, San Antonio and Miami, 1940-1965, 1985-1997 (Box 67, Folder 581A)
    - Ball-Rokeach, Sandra J., Presidential Grant, Media Portrayals of Social Science, 1983-1985 (Box 67, Folder 582)
    - Bane, Mary Jo and David T. Ellwood, Partial Support of Cross-City Comparative Study of Concentrated Urban Poverty, 998-919, 1989-1997 (Box 67, Folder 583)
    - Bartik, Timothy, Jobs for the Poor, Future of Work, 85-96-17, 1996-2001 (Box 67, Folder 584)
    - Bartik, Timothy, Jobs for the Poor, Future of Work, 85-96-17, 1996-2001 (Box 67, Folder 584A)
    - Bartik, Timothy, Jobs for the Poor, Future of Work, 85-96-17, Adendum, 1998-1999 (Box 67, Folder 585)
    - Baumol, William, Downsizing and Possible Consequences for Employment, Inequality and Profits, 85-97-07, 1996-1998 (Box 68, Folder 586)
    - Baumol, William, Downsizing and Possible Consequences for Employment, Inequality and Profits, 85-97-07, 1996-1998 (Box 68, Folder 586A)
    - Baumol, William and William Becker, Presidential Grant, For an Edited Volume,"Assessing Educational Practices: The Contribution of Economics", 988.933, 1991-1996 (Box 68, Folder 587)
    - Baumol, William and William Becker, Presidential Grant, For an Edited Volume,"Assessing Educational Practices: The Contribution of Economics", 988.933, 1991-1996 (Box 68, Folder 587A)
    - Beauchamp, Gary K., Cultural Influences on Flavor Perception, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 588)
    - Becker, Betsy Jane, Gender Difference in Science, 898.703, 1987-1991 (Box 68, Folder 589)
    - Becker, Betsy Jane, Gender Difference in Science, 898.703, 1987-1991 (Box 68, Folder 589A)
      Contains time sensitive material --- open in 2013
    - Becker, Betsy Jane, Gender Difference in Science, 898.703, Attachment File I, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 590)
    - Becker, Betsy Jane, Gender Difference in Science, 898.703, Attachment File II, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 591)
    - Behavioral Approaches to the Economics of Savings, Presidential Grant, A Workshop, 1992 March 27 (Box 68, Folder 592)
    - Bendick, Marc, Presidential Grant, Research on the Refinement of "Testing" Methodology for Research on Employment Discrimination, 998.969, 1991-1997 (Box 68, Folder 593)
    - Bendick, Marc, Presidential Grant, Research on the Refinement of "Testing" Methodology for Research on Employment Discrimination, 998.969, 1991-1997 (Box 68, Folder 593A)
      Contains time sensitive material --- open in 2017
    - Bendick, Marc, Presidential Grant, Research on the Refinement of "Testing" Methodology for Research on Employment Discrimination, 998.969, Attachment File, 1990-1996 (Box 69, Folder 594)
    - Bendick, Marc, Reviewing the Unites States Experience with Audits of the Labor Market Discrimination, 979.402, 1993-1996 (Box 69, Folder 595)
    - Bendick, Marc and Mary Lou Egan, "Training Against Employment Discrimination in the United States", 87-96-01, 1995-1999 (Box 69, Folder 596)
    - Bendick, Marc and Mary Lou Egan, "Training Against Employment Discrimination in the United States", 87-96-01, Correspondence, 1993-2002 (Box 69, Folder 597)
    - Bendick, Marc and Mary Lou Egan, "Training Against Employment Discrimination in the United States", 87-96-01, Correspondence, 1994-1998 (Box 70, Folder 598)
    - Bendick, Marc and Mary Lou Egan, "Training Against Employment Discrimination in the United States", 87-96-01, Work, 1989-1999 (Box 70, Folder 599)
    - Bermann, Barbara, Analyze the Public Expenditures for Early Childhood Welfare in France, 999.306, 1990-1996 (Box 70, Folder 600)